Thanks for watching!
Today, I'm going to have a lesson with
the director of the Uminomori Aquarium.
It's my first day.
I'm having a hard time wearing this wet
suit.
I have to learn how to wear it.
I'm going to practice more and more.
I hope I can do it smoothly.
I'm going to have a communication with
dolphins.
I want to show them a wonderful show.
I'm going to practice hard from today.
Please watch me.
Neko-Kichi, you are in the way.
Please subscribe my channel.
Oh my god
Keep doing that
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for your viewing.
It's hard to do it with your hands.
So, when you go up,
you have to hold it with your hands.
I finished my first day of practice.
I had a lot of things to do, but I was
so excited that the dolphins were so
cute.
When I gave them my autograph, they
jumped and were so cute.
I heard that they do a lot of dance and
lift, so I'm worried if I can do it.
I had a lot of things I couldn't do,
but I'll do my best to do something
nice.
I'm learning a lot and I'm working with
them, so I'll do my best.
I'm currently doing a visual shoot for
a collaboration event with Uminomori
Aquarium.
Everyone is wearing their own costumes.
It's like a workplace experience. It's
really fun.
Everyone has a face that looks like a
real staff member.
I heard that there will be a bedside
table on the day of the event.
I think I'm in the hut.
Everyone, please check it out.
I'm doing this with Uminomori Aquarium.
I'm glad to be able to do it with the
locals.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to swim with a dolphin for
the second time today.
I'm going to swim with a dolphin called
Coral.
I'm going to do my best.
She is cute.
Kaminarimon
finish
I haven't eaten a fountain in a while
Thank you for watching.
So, the second practice is over.
Thank you.
Today, I practiced dancing and drifting
with KORAL.
It was really difficult.
But KORAL has been with me many times
and taught me a lot.
I want to do my best to meet your
expectations.
I will do my best.
Today is the third practice.
Last time, I practiced dancing with
KORAL.
Today, I'm going to practice dancing
and continue the last lift.
I'm doing my best to do the last lift.
I want to do something new this time.
I will do my best with a smile so that
I can get closer to KORAL.
I will do my best.
Double, Winning, double
dragon horse
Romantic waltz
Thank you.
But I've come to understand.
I've made Koral do it many times.
What is the most difficult thing you've
done?
When I do this lift, my legs spread and
I'm fluttering.
So my goal is not to move my legs.
And for the dance, my arms stretch.
When I grab the fin, my arms stretch
and I'm like this.
So my goal is to tighten my arms and my
arms.
Today, I'm going to wear a wetsuit that
GO! made.
It's pink, so I'm a little embarrassed
to show it to you.
But it's really cute and I'm looking
forward to wearing it.
I'm a little embarrassed to show it to
you, but I'm sure you'll be surprised.
So I'm going to practice a lot while
studying various things.
I'm going to dance with you today and
I'm going to do my best to make the lift
look beautiful.
I'll do my best!
I don't know.
If your stand is not getting
postured...
Because your hips will push your waist
upwards,
your hip will be bent and you will be
disconnected by the pole.
Thank you for watching.
It's difficult.
I got another chance, so I'll practice
again.
I can't just float my legs before
touching the ice, so I'm struggling to
fix it.
So, I finished my fourth practice.
Thank you.
Today, I mainly practiced the lift.
I was going to wear the original weight
suit from May, but I couldn't do it
well.
So, I'm going to focus on the lift
today. I'm looking forward to the day
when I can wear it again.
When I watched the video, I was a
little confused because my waist was out
of the frame and I was afraid.
I'm getting used to it faster and
faster, and I'm trying to look forward
with a sparkling look.
Today is the fifth time?
It's the fifth practice.
This original sweatshirt will debut!
Yes, it's really shining, isn't it?
And there's a KINAYA mark here.
KINAYA said it looks like a ship.
I like that, so I'm happy.
So I'm going to wear this suit today.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm sure you'll be surprised by this
color.
During the break, I showed this suit to
the dolphins.
I think they were used to it.
I hope I can do my best while feeling
your warmth.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
The fifth practice is over.
Thank you very much.
Today, I wore the original sweatshirt
that I was given to make.
But, as I thought, KORAL is really
amazing.
As I repeated the number of times, I
realized that KORAL is amazing.
I could feel it and it was very
powerful.
I think it's really thanks to you.
I think I only have one chance to
perform.
I'm so happy that I can practice with
so many people.
But I want to do my best to not make
that happen.
You saw the show for the first time
today.
Yes, yes, yes.
How was it?
I was very impressed.
I cried.
Until now...
I was like, I want to swim! I want to
swim with dolphins!
I was really just curious about it.
I didn't know much about the actual
performance or how the dolphins swim.
I just practiced over and over again.
But when I saw it this time, I was
like...
I don't know...
I thought that performance was amazing.
The power that I received from that was
amazing.
I realized that this is a result of my
hard work.
I realized that this wouldn't have
happened without it.
But seeing that, I was able to jump
into the world I admired at that moment.
I wanted to do my best.
I didn't forget to be grateful and
smile.
I wanted to do my best.
I have a little practice left.
I will do my best to practice and
practice.
I will do my best to jump high.
I will do my best!
I finished the lesson with the practice
tutorial.
I did it about 6 times.
But, I really liked the dolphin, Coral.
The staff talked to me a lot when I had
free time.
I practiced 6 times in a flash.
I think I did my best.
I will do my best to improve myself as
much as possible.
I will participate in the dolphin show
on July 18th with Minomori Suizakka.
Please look forward to it.
I will do my best.
I will do my best for the show.
I would be happy if you could come and
see me.
I'm waiting for you at the aquarium.
Please come and see me.
Probably, a lot of small animals are
walking outside.
Do they know us?
Thank you for watching.